The Necklace is a drama film directed by Katya Hazel Boirand.
A glimpse into a young woman's life as she navigates coping with a chronic auto-immune
condition whilst attempting to form intimate, romantic connections.
Lucy goes about her dating life with an unexpected twist at the end.
Lucy, played by Katya Hazel Boirand.
Dom, played by Alexi Armitage.
Sarah, played by Kim Spearman.
Peter, played by Tom Swale.
The Affair of the Diamond Necklace (French: Affaire du collier de la reine, "Affair of the Queen's Necklace") was an incident
from 1784 to 1785 at the court of King Louis XVI of France that involved his wife, Queen Marie Antoinette.
The queen's reputation, already tarnished by gossip, was further sullied by the false accusation that she had participated in a
crime to defraud the Crown's jewellers in acquiring a very expensive diamond necklace she then refused to pay for.
In reality, she had rejected the idea of buying it only to have her
signature forged by Jeanne de Valois-Saint-Rémy.
Although Valois-Saint-Rémy was later convicted, the event remains historically significant as one of many that led to the French disillusionment with
the monarchy, in that it was one of the contemporary scandals that gave moral weight and popular support for the French Revolution.
The tone is mind_bending.